export default data9 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Who is the patron Saint of England?",
        options: ["St George", "St Patrick", "St David", "St Andrew"],
        correct_option: "St George"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Where is Loch Lomond and the Trossachs National Park located?",
        options: ["England", "Wales", "Scotland", "Northern Ireland"],
        correct_option: "Scotland"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "Wales has its own established church.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "What stories are associated with Geoffrey Chaucer?",
        options: ["The Cambridge Tales", "The Eastbourne Tales", "The Canterbury Tales", "The London Tales"],
        correct_option: "The Canterbury Tales"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "When is Boxing Day celebrated?",
        options: ["31st October", "26th December", "24th December", "01st January"],
        correct_option: "26th December"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "What is the name of the holiday when banks and many other businesses are closed for the day?",
        options: ["Credit Holidays", "Branch Holidays", "Bank Holidays", "Business Holidays"],
        correct_option: "Bank Holidays"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "What do you need to drive in the UK?",
        options: ["An ‘L’ plate", "A National Insurance Number", "A valid driving licence", "An ‘R’ plate"],
        correct_option: "A valid driving licence"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "What is the Home Secretary responsible for?",
        options: ["Health", "Defence", "Education", "Policing"],
        correct_option: "Policing"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "Where does “the Fringe” festival take place?",
        options: ["Fraserburgh", "Edinburgh", "Inverness", "St Andrews"],
        correct_option: "Edinburgh"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "How many members does the Welsh government have?",
        options: ["150", "120", "90", "60"],
        correct_option: "60"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "The names or photographs of  young people found guilty of a crime can be published in newspapers or used by the media.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "What was Edward Elgar famous for?",
        options: ["He was a musician", "He was a tennis player", "He was a comedian", "He was an actor"],
        correct_option: "He was a musician"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "Which of the following is not a British banknote?",
        options: ["£50", "£25", "£20", "£5"],
        correct_option: "£25"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Where does the Scottish Grand National take place?",
        options: ["Fife", "Edinburgh", "Ayr", "St Andrews"],
        correct_option: "Ayr"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "When did the UK join the EU?",
        options: ["In 1957", "In 1973", "In 1975", "In 1964"],
        correct_option: "In 1973"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "What did Emmeline Pankhurst fight for?",
        options: ["The right to liberty and security", "The right for women to vote", "Freedom of expression", "The right to a fair trial"],
        correct_option: "The right for women to vote"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "What was Isaac Newton known for?",
        options: ["The discovery of insulin", "The discovery of gravity", "The discovery of penicillin", "The discovery of steam power"],
        correct_option: "The discovery of gravity"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "When did the WWI come to an end?",
        options: ["In 1922", "In 1918", "In 1945", "In 1943"],
        correct_option: "In 1918"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Who built a wall in the north of England to keep out the Picts (ancestors of the Scottish people)?",
        options: ["Boudicca", "Emperor Hadrian", "Emperor Claudius", "Julius Caesar"],
        correct_option: "Emperor Hadrian"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "Does Britain have a written constitution?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "No"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "The devolved governments in Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland cannot control policies and laws governing taxation and social security:",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "What percentage of the total British population is located in Scotland?",
        options: ["Over 30%", "Over 5%", "Over 8%", "Over 3%"],
        correct_option: "Over 8%"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Which of the following academy awards are the equivalent of the Oscars in the UK?",
        options: ["The Brit Awards", "The BAFTA Awards", "The Mercury Music Prize", "The MTV Awards"],
        correct_option: "The BAFTA Awards"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Which political party was elected after the Second World War?",
        options: ["The Liberal Democrats", "The Green Party", "The Conservative Party", "The Labour Party"],
        correct_option: "The Labour Party"
    },
    
]